Paresh Maheshwari

🔀 pareshsurya721@gmail.com 📞 +918866124701 🛮 in paresh-maheshwari1 🎧 Paresh-Maheshwari

Reportfolio Vadodara, Gujarat, India

Profile

I am currently pursuing a B.Tech degree in Computer Science with a specialization in Cyber Security. My passion lies in ethical hacking and Security Operations Center (SOC) operations. I'm building a strong foundation in Vulnerability Assessment, Penetration Testing, and Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) solutions. I'm dedicated to enhancing digital system security.

Professional Experience

Cybersecurity Intern, Senselearner Technologies Pvt. Ltd

06/2023 - 08/2023

- Explored cyber threats, incident response, risk management, and compliance.
- Contributed to collaborative projects during the internship.
- Gained a holistic understanding of cybersecurity.

Future Ready Talent Internship

04/2023 - 05/2023

- Learned in-demand Azure Cloud & Security skills aligned to industry needs
- Earned a certificate from Microsoft AZ-900, PL-900, AI-900
- Received a certificate from Microsoft and NASSCOM

Education

B.Tech Computer Science and Engineering (Cyber Security),

Parul Institute of Technology ☑

10/2020 - present Vadodara, India

Skills

Penetration-Testing • Burp-Suite • Web-Application Security • OWASP • Python • Cyber-Security Vulnerability-Assessment ● Networking ● Linux Command line and Scriting ● Splunk ● Log analysis Wireshark • Nmap • CompTIA Security • Cloud Computing • Digital Forensis • Nessus Metasploit

Certificates

Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)

Microsoft

Ethical Hacking Essentials

(EHE) 🗷 EC-council

Ethical Hacker 🗷

Cisco

Azure AI Fundamentals (AI-

900) 🗗 Microsoft

NSE 1 Network Security

Associate 🛮 fortinet

Linux Privilege Escalation ☑

TCM Security

Ethical Hacking: Wireless

Networks 7 LinkedIn

Security Analyst Bootcamp 🛮 Virtually Testing Foundation

Cybersecurity Fundamentals

Ø IBM